

Josep Phyto Napitupulu

Software Engineer

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/josepnapitupulu/ 🜎 https://github.com/josepnapitupulu

G Portofolio

A 5-semester student at the Del Institute of Technology, majoring in Bachelor of Applied Technology Software Engineering. Dedicated to developing skills in the field of Software Engineering. As a deep student interested in Software Engineering, I am always enthusiastic to learn and understand every project that I build so that I can provide services with the highest quality standards. My experience as Software Engineer from a campus project has given me valuable insights intohow the process of developing an application or website with various programming languages so that it can be used by many people and is useful for the environment that uses it. Being active in several organizations and communities has further enhanced my abilities teamwork and time management skills, along with cultivating strong leadership abilities.

Education

07/2021 - present

Del Institute of Technology,

Bachelor of Applied Software Engineering Technology *∂* GPA 3.49/4.00

Languages

Indonesia

English

Skills

PHP • Laravel • Java Script • Java • Kotlin • Golang • C • SQL • HTML • CSS • Figma

Flutter • Draw Io • Postman

Project Experience

01/2023 - 07/2023

Software Engineer,

HKBP Palmarum Administration and Finance Website | Del Institute of Technology

- Develop and design systems from the HKBP Palmarum website. Build an MVP with great features in 5 months
- Build website appearance.
- Build an API using the Laravel framework.
- Improve service to deal with bugs that may occur.
- service and database design.
- the website is built using laravel farmwork, php, html, css, js.

03/2023 - 05/2023

Software Engineer,

HKBP Palmarum Administration Mobile Application | Del Institute of Technology

- Develop and design systems from the HKBP Palmarum website. using the MVC concept for 3 months.
- Build application views.
- Build an API using the Golang programming language.
- Build application features and functions.
- · Service and database design.
- The website is built using the Laravel and Golang framework languages.

03/2023 - 05/2023

Software Engineer, HKBP Palmarum Website | Del Institute of Technology

- Develop and design systems from the HKBP Palmarum website. using the MVC concept for 3 months.
- Build application views.
- Build an API using the Golang programming language.
- Build application features and functions.
- Service and database design.
- The website is built using the Laravel and Golang framework languages.

10/2022 - 12/2022

Software Engineer, Console Based Food Ordering | Del Institute of Technology

- Designing and building console-based application functions.
- Build order features, totals, quantity of items available, and changes in quantities if already ordered.
- Using MVC features.
- Console applications are built using the Java programming language.

01/2022 - 06/2022

Software Engineer, Brew Brothers Coffee Website | Del Institute of Technology

- Develop and design systems from the Brew Brothers Coffee website. using the MVC concept for 6 months.
- Build application views.
- Analyze and design website features from the results of requirements gathering.
- Build website features and functions both on the user and on the admin.
- Service and database design.
- The website is built using the Laravel framework language and PHP, HTML, CSS, JS.

Organizations

06/2023 - 06/2024

Department of Science and Technology, Head of Department

10/2022 - present

Radio Del Club, Member